# **Henry Siau**

Full-stack Web Developer, AWS Certified Developer, with two years of experience. Deeply knowledgeable in a wide variety of computer languages. Strong communicator and is flexible with scheduling.

Palo Alto, CA 94306 (415) 910-4174 siauhenry@gmail.com www.henrysiau.com LinkedIn Github

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Skipcard**, San Francisco, CA — Full-Stack Developer

Aug 2018 - Aug 2020

Responsible for developing new features and maintaining the codebase for the client-side and server-side application using React, Redux, Node.js, and MongoDB.

Built coupon system, perks system, and email notification system, added Google map integration, enrich user information with Clearbit.

Contributed 231k ++ 122k-- lines of code

worked directly under CTO.

## Lexus of Serramonte, Colma, CA — Sales Consultant

Sep 2015 - Jul 2017

Consistently ranked top 20% by sales performance, maintained elite-level customer satisfaction every month.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Udacity,** Mountain View, CA — Full Stack Web Developer Nanodegree

Aug 2017 - Feb 2018

Technology acquired: Python, HTML, CSS, SQL, JavaScript, Flask, sqlAlchemy, Postgresql, JQuery.

# **Guangdong Polytechnic Normal University** — Bachelors

Sep 2005 - Jul 2010

Major: E-commerce

Core curriculum: Data Structure and Algorithm in Java, Relational Data Base, Computer Network, OOP, Software Design Pattern, E-commerce Marketing, E-commerce Security.

#### **SKILLS**

Node.js / JavaScript

React / Redux / Express.js

HTML / CSS

PostgreSQL / MongoDB / Redis

**AWS** 

Python / Flask / Django

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

AWS Certified Developer -Nov 2020 - Nov 2023

Score: 937 out of 1000

The score needed to pass this exam is 720